You are
the most popular person in the city.
Why do you like me?
I don't know.
I only know
I'm happy
when you're around,
and I'm upset
when you're not.
Really?
But you were
gonna marry Ms. Yan.
If I asked you to marry me directly,
would you tear me apart?
Yes.
That's why
I asked Yicheng to hire you.
So I could see you again.
Wait.
So you planned
for me to go to Ning'an?
And the escort robbery?
That's not my fault.
It's just
a coincidence.
No,
it's destiny.
You're gonna marry into my family.
Don't get it wrong.
You're the son-in-law of the Sus.
And I'm
the son-in-law of the Chengs.
Anyway,
I belong to you.
You belong to me.
You are so slick.
Have you
ever said that to someone else?
Ouch.
Please be kind to me.
I swear to you.
I've never said that to anyone else.
I didn't even use force.
Does it hurt?
No, no.
Are you okay?
We're here.
I'm so happy today.
Well, I...
[You big blockhead,]
[finally getting a bit smarter.]
[I should take the initiative.]
Xin,
I want to spend every Qixi Festival
I want to spend it with you.
I want to spend every day with you.
My Lord,
it's all my fault.
I insisted on persuading you to come back
for a peaceful life.
Although Su Biaotou
is the only woman you ever liked,
she is unkind to you.
Don't blame us for being unfaithful.
Yeah.
My Lord.
You are the White Wolf.
As long as you say it,
we will do whatever you want.
Whether it's to take Su back
or to kill Cheng Qi.
Or we can take the escort
and go back to the mountains when they are not here.
We can do both things.
You two
You haven't even killed a chicken.
Shut up.
I'll go.
Okay.
Go pack up.
My dear,
can't we talk about it tomorrow?
We should give him an explanation.
Fine.
Don't talk too long, my dear.
I know, my dear.
Wait for me outside.
Looks like you're planning to leave.
Yes.
We'll leave after the contest.
No matter the result,
I'm grateful for your help.
The debt is settled.
Take care.
My Lord,
we're about to leave.
Why bother with the contest?
A man's word is his bond.
I promised her.
I must do it.
Miss Zhang.
My Lord.
I've never seen them with that before.
It's just a few hidden weapons.
Too old-fashioned.
Put on the newly made soft armor.
Yes.
Bro, are these things gonna work?
Maybe we should just fight them straight up.
I spent several nights making this.
I trust your setup,
no problem.
If you say so,
it must be fine.
What's going on?
Just a few days and you're siding with them?
Am I still your closest brother?
Of course you are.
But, brother,
you should check your trap.
That's more like it.
He's right.
Okay.
Stop, stop, it hurts!
Stop beating, stop beating!
I surrender, I surrender!
I'll never do it again, I'll never do it again!
Good.
Well done.
Slow down.
Gong Xi,
you need to slow him down.
If you can't win, don't force yourself.
How can you say that before the match?
Dabao,
it's my turn, right?
Easy.
Gong Xi, slip away.
Don't let him get close to you.
If you win this,
you can pick any candy shop in Yunjing.
You're so nice.
Gong Xi, be careful.
Good.
It's hard.
Don't worry.
We can win.
Here we go.
Hey.
Come on.
Gong Xi, don't fall off the stage.
Good job.
Gong Xi.
Come on.
Very good.
Where's the candy?
Gong Xi.
I should've brought Da Bao candy sooner.
See if the people from the government office have arrived.
My lord.
Go!
Don't hold back!
How dangerous!
My lord,
you are the outlaw wanted by the government.
White Wolf.
Using hidden weapons is one thing,
but to slander us after losing a fight is another.
It's outrageous.
He's the one who robbed our escort before.
We never robbed your escort.
Fine.
Then you must have robbed someone else's.
My lord,
he is the White Wolf.
He is the White Wolf.
He doesn't look like it.
How dare you, White Wolf.
Give up the resistance.
You have no evidence.
How can you frame an innocent person?
Mr. Su
Are you trying to cover up for the bandit?
It's really him.
Or
are you colluding with the bandits?
Whether it's true or false,
we'll know after the trial.
Take him.
Colluding with bandits?
Oh, no.
The White Wolf is threatening Su.
It's really the White Wolf.
Don't move.
Or I'll kill her.
Please don't move.
Don't hurt my wife.
My lord,
don't be fooled by them.
They are in the same boat.
In the capital of the Yun State,
can't officials protect the people?
The Sus escorted goods for generations.
They must have been tricked by the bandits.
Yes, they must have been tricked.
It must be a misunderstanding.
The Su's Escort Agency
must have been deceived.
Yes, it must be a misunderstanding.
My lord,
is it the White Wolf?
Take them back for interrogation.
Take them away.
Yes.
Investigate thoroughly.
Guys.
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
Be careful.
Chase them.
Don't let them get away.
Yes.
Go.
Lady
are you okay?
My lady.
Mr. Su,
our contest is not over yet.
Now we can settle it one on one.
Ying,
remind them of what I told them.
Got it.
You want to fight, huh?
I'll play along.
According to the rules,
she can only fight with me.
How can you say that?
Shameless!
Shut up!
Mr. Fu is right.
Trust is the escort agency's top priority.
These businessmen are invited to be witnesses today.
There must be rules
and results.
Don't say I bully women.
Su Yuejiao,
you can stop now.
You give up?
Give up?
No way.
I'll do it.
Jiaojiao.
My lady,
be careful.
Stop!
Stop it!
Jiaojiao.
My lady.
The people who escaped
were all dressed in the clothes of the Su's Escort Agency.
Take all the people of the Su's Escort Agency here.
Yes.
Wait.
Miss Zhang.
I can guarantee with my life
that Mr. Su
has nothing to do with the evil deeds of those bandits.
Please help him.
I will repay you
in the future.
Mr. Lu.
Miss Zhang.
The Sus
are hard to escape from this.
But Mr. Su is injured.
Why don't you let them go back to the escort agency
and keep them there?
What do you think?
Well...
If you have any concerns,
I can ask my father for an order.
No, no, no.
These are trivial matters.
No need to bother the Grand Preceptor.
You guys,
escort them back to the agency.
No one is allowed to leave.
-Yes. -Yes.
My lord, you've worked hard today.
Why don't you go to Huayue Tower for a meal
before going back?
Well...
I'll take your advice.
Thank you for your hospitality.
I'll take my leave.
Jiaojiao.
Thank you for your help.
I just want to know
how you're going to repay me.
You just let them go like this?
Zhang Xi Yun has spoken.
I don't know what she's up to.
Let's wait and see.
Miss Zhang,
may I return to the escort agency first?
Oh?
Shouldn't you come back to the villa with me?
Now that Su Biaotou's life is uncertain,
she has done me a favor.
I can't just ignore it.
It's also bad for the Nebula leader's reputation.
Fine, go ahead.
I'll come for you another day.
Thank you, Miss Zhang.
Farewell.
Yicheng,
go find Meng Feifei
and have her keep an eye on Bai Yanliang.
Make sure he doesn't go to the agency.
Okay, okay.
Hurry up.
That's how Yu got sick.
That's how it was back then.
Grandpa,
Jiaojiao has been tough since childhood.
She'll be fine.
Grandpa,
the doctor said
there was no damage to the tendons.
If she can get through these days,
she'll recover.
Grandpa,
you should go back and rest.
I'll stay with her.
Jiao,
you haven't stamped your palm,
and we haven't gone home to see our parents.
You can't have anything wrong.
Do you know?
Look at this.
Oh, this one is good.
These two are both pretty.
How does it taste?
-Listen to me.  -Let me see.
It's good.
Thank you, my sister.
Follow me.
She's still stuck in the escort agency.
I have to save her.
The young master said
you can't go.
Why?
How are you going to save her?
By acupuncture and decoction?
or get caught by the soldiers?
I can't just leave.
Don't let the Sus get involved.
Just save her.
No one can get in or out.
Sir, it's me.
It's you.
You won 3 taels of silver
from me in the game last time.
I didn't recognize you.
This is
to make amends to you.
That's more like it.
What do you want to do?
I'm craving for wine.
I'll be back in four hours.
The deputy said
no one can go out.
He's going to fight against bandits.
You know
I never go out of the Imperial City.
How could I have anything to do with bandits?
I just want to eat something good.
I'll bring you
the best wine from Huayue Tower.
Go and come back quickly.
Thank you very much.
Be gentle.
Wasn't it agreed before
to teach Su Yuejiao a lesson?
When I become the head of the Escort Agency,
I'll give you all the escort business in the city.
How could you hurt her so badly?
And now the entire escort agency is shut down.
It wasn't me who colluded with the bandits.
She brought this on herself.
Yeah.
That's because I told you all this.
You better tell the authorities
and let us all go.
You?
tell me what to do?
What do you mean?
What Bai Yanliang did
has nothing to do with us.
If he can't be caught,
the government won't let your family go.
At that time,
if you're not killed,
you can come to Fuyun Escort Agency for a living.
When I take your business,
I won't be afraid of having one more useless person.
You...
You what?
You are just a traitor!
Humph!
Get out of here!
Fu Xiang,
I'll kill you!
Gloria.
You're awake.
Do you want some water?
Be careful.
Is everyone okay?
Everyone's fine.
Only you are in trouble.
You don't need to worry about others.
You've been unconscious.
Your grandfather and brother are worried about you.
What about Bai Yanli?
He ran away with his brother.
It seems that
he is the real White Wolf.
Although he is reckless,
he is not unforgivable.
I gave him a hint before,
so he kidnapped you
to get rid of your relationship.
Otherwise,
we should all be in jail.
I should have thought of it earlier.
When we were preparing for the contest,
I felt his moves were somewhat familiar.
Now that I think about it,
he must be the one who robbed the wedding.
It was me who kept him at the escort agency.
It was me who ruined the escort agency.
Don't overthink it.
Focus on recovering first.
As for the escort agency,
I'll figure it out.
He's a brigand.
What can you do?
You forget
my father was a county sheriff.
I have some connections
in the officialdom.
Now,
as long as we can prove
that Bai Yanliang's actions
have nothing to do with the escort agency,
we'll be fine.
Jia
Don't worry.
I will protect the Escort Agency for you.
Sir,
may I ask
if my son Li Shi went out today?
I can't find him anywhere.
We didn't see your son,
and we didn't let him out to drink.
Sir,
Sir.
Good wine.
Come and try it.
As happy as a god.
Try it.
Come in.
I don't need your help.
I am
the head escort of Su's Escort Agency.
You...
This is my mother's agency.
Fu Xiang,
what are you?
You broke your promise
and treated me like a dog.
Gong Xi, Fa Cai.
Grandpa.
Take him inside.
Call the others to the hall.
Yes.
Hurry up.
Li Shi,
have you slept enough?
What did you do this afternoon?
Li Shi,
what did you do this afternoon?
Tell me,
what did you do?
Dad.
Dad
I...
Why did you let her out?
She just woke up.
Don't catch a cold.
I wanted to come here.
Grandpa
He just went out for a walk.
It's my fault
that the escort agency was closed.
You want to take over the escort agency,
and now you want to take over the blame.
Su Yuejiao,
the escort agency doesn't belong to you alone.
Yes,
I didn't listen to you,
and insisted on taking part in the contest.
I don't deserve to be the head.
The escort agency is yours,
mine,
Mine!
Dad.
It's my fault.
I'm sorry.
You...
Did you just go out to find Fu Xiang?
I was stupid.
I shouldn't have trusted that jerk Fu Xiang,
and told him about Bai Yanliang's identity,
letting him ruin the agency.
But I never intended to hurt Jiaojiao,
let alone destroy the agency.
Dad, what should we do?
Dad.
What should we do?
Did you really do all this
for the agency?
You were never fit to be the head.
Now it seems
you don't deserve it at all.
Our agency is a family.
I filled those accounts for you
because I didn't want outsiders to look down on the Su family
and our agency.
Now it seems
that competition was a setup.
Since we've already gotten involved,
who's right and who's wrong
doesn't matter anymore.
We are a family
behind closed doors.
We should discuss how to get through the tough times together.
Su Li, do you know you were wrong?
Dad, I know I was wrong.
How did you know about Bai Yanliang's identity?
Bai Yanliang likes Jiaojiao.
He was stood up by you on Qixi Festival.
His brother persuaded him to leave.
I overheard it.
So, except for what you heard,
Fu Xiang doesn't have any other evidence.
Without proof of Bai Yanliang's involvement,
the court
can't easily convict the escort agency.
Jiaojiao,
are you willing to forgive your uncle?
I'm not.